Who do you trust?
Before I Go to Sleep is a thriller, mystery film directed by Rowan Joffé.
A woman wakes up every day, remembering nothing as a
result of a traumatic accident in her past.
One day, new terrifying truths emerge that force
her to question everyone around her.
Christine, played by Nicole Kidman.
Ben, played by Colin Firth.
Dr. Nasch, played by Mark Strong.
Warehouse Caretaker, played by Ben Crompton.
Claire, played by Anne-Marie Duff.
Ben, played by Adam Levy.
Before I Go to Sleep is a 2014 mystery psychological thriller film written and
directed by Rowan Joffé and based on the 2011 novel of the same name by S.
An international co-production between the United Kingdom, the United States, France and
Sweden, the film stars Nicole Kidman, Mark Strong, Colin Firth, and Anne-Marie Duff.
The film explores themes of amnesia, married couple,
head injury, flashback, confusion.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.